# RODRIGO CÁCERES GARZÓN

#### **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

11209 Richland Avenue, Los Ángeles, CA 90064 rodrigocaceresgarzon94@gmail.com

(+1) 310 254 0 264

rodrigocaceresgarzon.myportfolio.com

Graphic designer specialized in brand creation, development, and maintenance; oriented to innovation, sustainability, and inclusion. Through strategic design and communication skills, I propose projects to solve them clearly and effectively, to make a memorable and unique brand with a special essence.



## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **CORNERSTONE GROUP:**

- CORNERSTONE
- CAREER PARTNERS
- CL SELECTION

GRAPHIC DESIGNER FREELANCE **APRIL 2020 - JULY 2021** 

GRAPHIC DESIGNER **AUGUST 2019 - MARCH 2020** 

GRAPHIC DESIGNER INTERN JANUARY 2019 - JULY 2019

- Creation and development of brand identity
- Design of advertising and brand material
- Design and implementation of social media strategy
- Development of internal and external communication
- Development of audiovisual material
- International support designer
- Marketing area support

### **FLOWFFY CLOTHING**

GRAPHIC DESIGNER
SEPTEMBER 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2020

- Creation and development of the brand from scratch
- Brand identity design
- Creation of audiovisual material
- Design of publications for social networks
- Social media administration
- E-commerce website design



# **EDUCATION**

UNIVERSIDAD SAN IGNACIO DE LOYOLA - LIMA, PERÚ PROFESSIONAL DEGREE ARTE Y DISEÑO EMPRESARIAL	2021
UNIVERSIDAD SAN IGNACIO DE LOYOLA - LIMA, PERÚ BACHELOR DEGREE ARTE Y DISEÑO EMPRESARIAL	2019
SAN IGNACIO UNIVERSITY - MIAMI, EEUU MARKETING	2017
SOCIAL MEDIA GRAPHIC DESIGN	<b>JUNE 2020</b>
ADOBE PREMIERE: POST PRODUCTION	JUNE 2020
E-COMMERCE FOR BEGINNERS	JUNE 2020
DIGITAL MARKETING ON FACEBOOK: GROW YOUR BUSINESS	JUNE 2020
AFTER EFFECTS: CREATE DIFFERENT MINIMALIST ANIMATIONS	JULY 2020
BRANDING: CREATE A VISUAL IDENTITY	AUGUST 2020
BRANDING: OFF ROAD	OCTOBER 2020
MARKETING WITH INFLUENCERS	OCTOBER 2020



**ENGLISH** 

**KAPLAN INTERNATIONAL LANGUAGES** 

2021

**LEVEL: C2 - PROFICIENCY** 

LANGUAGES

**PORTUGUESE** 

**CERTIFICATE IN ADVANCED LANGUAGE** 

2014



# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- BRANDING

- ILLUSTRATOR

- ADVERTISING

- PREMIERE PRO

- VIDEO EDITION

- AFTER EFFECTS

- ANIMATION

- PHOTOSHOP

- PHOTOGRAPHY

- INDESIGN



**SPORT OPERATION** 

**LIMA 2019 PARAPAN AMERICAN GAMES** 

2019

**VOLUNTEERING** 

KAPLAN AMBASSADOR

**KAPLAN INTERNATIONAL LANGUAGES** 

2021